Joshua Kelly

Software Developer - Meaningful Use

Providence Village, TX - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Joshua-Kelly/6c7cc17233ab5e80

Software Developer maintains a stable work ethic, which has been fine-tuned in both structured and independent work environments. Offers a strong background in analysis and logic gained through higher level mathematics and applied programming skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Meaningful Use - Lewisville, TX - April 2014 to Present

Stages 1 and 2), CPOE, EMR, EHR, ICD-9/ICD-10, Report Writing, Clinical data, Financial Analytics.

Math Skills: Regression, Abstract and Linear Algebra, Ordinary and Partial Differential Equations, Topology and Real Analysis, and Game Theory (not a comprehensive list).

Experience

Software Developer

Interface People - Lewisville, TX April 2014 - Present

Constructed and debugged T-SQL objects. Helped maintain and enhance an ETL process used for Meaningful Use. Optimized SQL logic and performance. Performed data validation between Meditech and the company's data repository and data warehouse. Contributed to a data analytics product for hospitals. Took on Scrum Master duties. Helped write and maintain Windows desktop applications in .Net. Redesigned and implemented database architecture for web application to view sensitive patient information. Composed several technical documents describing the standards for this implementation in addition to providing automated testing for the procedures and dynamic queries.

Associate Software Engineer

Madison Technology Systems - Madison, MS - August 2013 to April 2014

Wrote and debugged programs for hospital reports in Meditech Magic and NPR Report Writer. Constructed a scheduler in a .Net WPF desktop application utilizing the Quartz.Net package for a larger company project. Built an application which dynamically moves text from an HTML format to a SQL database.

EDUCATION

B.S. in Mathematics

Oklahoma Baptist University - Shawnee, OK April 2000 to May 2012

M.S. in Mathematics

Jackson State University - Jackson, MS April 2000